<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>bash - Category - Juan Gabriel Machuca</title>
        <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/categories/bash/</link>
        <description>bash - Category - Juan Gabriel Machuca</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 21:02:15 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juanmachuca95.github.io/categories/bash/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Let&#39;s talk about gorutines</title>
    <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/lets_talk_about_gorutines/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 21:02:15 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Juan Gabriel Machuca</author>
    <guid>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/lets_talk_about_gorutines/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I have to say that my relationship with the goruntins not is the bests, However, I am deeply attracted to gorutins.
Ok, let&rsquo;s skip the romantic part and get down to the nitty-gritty.
I have a dream I have a dream? Yes, this question should be &ldquo;I have a problem&rdquo;, but it&rsquo;s not enought funny to admit that I do.
In an ideal world I would have a lot of heavy tasks, running concurrently that I could cancel at any time, without worrying about memory leaks, race conditions or synchronization scheduling.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to deploy theme LoveIt in GitHub Pages</title>
    <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/how_to_deploy_theme_loveit_in_github_pages/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 19:46:43 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Juan Gabriel Machuca</author>
    <guid>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/how_to_deploy_theme_loveit_in_github_pages/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[My blog uses hugo with the LoveIt theme that I use to publish this post and all deployed on GitHub Pages. So, in this post we are going to talk about how we can do that.
1 Requeriments: First of all, we need a couple of things before we start, here is my list.
 You have to install hugo 👉 Installation  Read documentation of the amazing LoveIt theme LoveIt  Read notes GitHubPages   2 Setup First of all we need to setup project in local, this firsts step you can see also in basic configuration # Create hugo site hugo new site demo_hugo # Move to directory cd demo_hugo git init # add theme LoveIt git submodule add https://github.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
