<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Juan Gabriel Machuca</title>
        <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Juan Gabriel Machuca</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 16:26:09 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>What&#39;s up with generics in Go? Part 1</title>
    <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/whats_up_generics_in_go_part_1/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 16:26:09 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Juan Gabriel Machuca</author>
    <guid>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/whats_up_generics_in_go_part_1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ðŸ“ A lot of water passed under the bridge since Generics came to Golang. This water did not pass in front of me, but today, together, let&rsquo;s rediscover &ldquo;Generics&rdquo; ðŸ’ª.
What is Generics? Go is a statically and strongly typed programming language. This means that variables must be declared with a specific type and this type cannot change during program execution. In addition, operations on variables and expressions must be type compatible.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to use i18n in golang?</title>
    <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/how_to_use_i18n_in_golang/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 11:26:08 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Juan Machuca</author>
    <guid>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/how_to_use_i18n_in_golang/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hi, it&rsquo;s me again. I may not keep my promise to do a post every month, but in my defense I had to move to another place, which made it harder to pay attention to the blog. Anyway, I&rsquo;m back, to continue.
Today we are going to talk about i18n. I have to say that it is very interesting for me, because I didn&rsquo;t know much about it. So . .]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Let&#39;s talk about gorutines</title>
    <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/lets_talk_about_gorutines/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 21:02:15 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Juan Gabriel Machuca</author>
    <guid>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/lets_talk_about_gorutines/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I have to say that my relationship with the goruntins not is the bests, However, I am deeply attracted to gorutins.
Ok, let&rsquo;s skip the romantic part and get down to the nitty-gritty.
I have a dream I have a dream? Yes, this question should be &ldquo;I have a problem&rdquo;, but it&rsquo;s not enought funny to admit that I do.
In an ideal world I would have a lot of heavy tasks, running concurrently that I could cancel at any time, without worrying about memory leaks, race conditions or synchronization scheduling.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How to deploy theme LoveIt in GitHub Pages</title>
    <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/how_to_deploy_theme_loveit_in_github_pages/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 19:46:43 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Juan Gabriel Machuca</author>
    <guid>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/how_to_deploy_theme_loveit_in_github_pages/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[My blog uses hugo with the LoveIt theme that I use to publish this post and all deployed on GitHub Pages. So, in this post we are going to talk about how we can do that.
1 Requeriments: First of all, we need a couple of things before we start, here is my list.
 You have to install hugo ðŸ‘‰ Installation Read documentation of the amazing LoveIt theme LoveIt Read notes GitHubPages  2 Setup First of all we need to setup project in local, this firsts step you can see also in basic configuration]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Introduction to MyBlog</title>
    <link>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/intoduction_to_my_blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:04:08 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Juan Gabriel Machuca</author>
    <guid>https://juanmachuca95.github.io/posts/intoduction_to_my_blog/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Â¡Hi everyone! This is my first posts, I have to say that my english is not very good and it is one the reasons why I started to write my blog.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
